

111-4 Juana Osmena Extension Purok 8 Kamputhaw, Cebu City +63928 044 5382



anthonybasamot@gmail.com

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm a newly registered architect, but I've been doing freelance work for 5 years now. I've worked with foreign clients from the United States, the U.K., and Australia.

I am currently transitioning into the tech industry as I am currently experiencing a quarter life crisis in my current line of work. I'm seeking a change of direction that will challenge me and provide growth based on the effort I put in.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### JUNIOR ARCHITECT

Architect DJP | March 2019 - June 2021

Completed 2 years of architectural apprenticeship, and exposed in space planning, design conceptualization, site supervision, detailing of architectural plans, interior designing and detailing, architectural walkthrough/animations, interior and exterior visualizations.

### FREELANCE 3D VISUALIZER

Fiverr | Sep 2017 - Sep 2022

### Named as Top-rated Freelancer on Fiverr.com

5-year experience working with clients from all over the globe, mostly from the United States, U.K, Canada, Australia, and New Zealand

Mostly Exposed in building envelope designing, interior designing, architectural walkthrough/animations, interior and exterior visualizations.

#### **EDUCATION**

TERTIARY EDUCATION: 2014 - 2019

Cebu Institute of Technology - University Bachelor of Science in Architecture

Top 6 Architectural Thesis Writing and Exhibit Archinext HCG Scholar Dean's List (1st Year)

### QUALIFICATION:

Licensed Architect Professional Regulation Commission, Philippines

June 2022

## **CERTIFICATES:**

Autodesk AutoCad Training Completion Autodesk Revit Training Completion

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

	Beginner	Advance
Design Skills	Reginner	Advance
Planning		
Project Magement		
Research		
Math		
Computer Skills		
Communication		